totalgamingnetwork.com 2019-12-04

# Privacy Policy - Total Gaming Network

Effective date: January 06, 2019

Total Gaming Network ("us", "we", or "our") operates the [https://totalgamingnetwork.com](https://totalgamingnetwork.com/) website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from [https://totalgamingnetwork.com](https://totalgamingnetwork.com/).

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

## Types of Data Collected

### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

> • Email address  
>  • Cookies and Usage Data

We also collect information from you when you voluntarily provide such information. Information you share may contain personally identifying information, and may include, but not be limited to, information such as your username, email address, and any messages or images you share through the use of our Services. 

### Usage Data

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

> **• Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.  
>  **• Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.  
>  **• Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

Total Gaming Network uses the collected data for various purposes:

> • To provide and maintain the Service  
>  • To notify you about changes to our Service  
>  • To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so  
>  • To provide customer care and support  
>  • To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service  
>  • To monitor the usage of the Service • To detect, prevent and address technical issues

## Data Retention

To dispose of personal data, we may anonymize it or take other appropriate steps. Some data may be retained where there is a reason to restrict the processing of data instead of deleting it. In such instances, we may anonymize the data rather than deleting it. Data may persist in copies made for backup and business continuity purposes for additional time.

Total Gaming Network members located in the EU may choose to withdraw consent by unchecking the privacy consent box on this page: <https://totalgamingnetwork.com/settings/privacy>

Members choosing to withdraw consent will have their data automatically deleted after a period of three days. A user may re-consent by logging back in to their account and re-checking the consent box during this period of time.

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Total Gaming Network will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Legal Requirements

Total Gaming Network may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

> • To comply with a legal obligation  
>  • To protect and defend the rights or property of Total Gaming Network  
>  • To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service  
>  • To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public  
>  • To protect against legal liability

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

## Advertising

We may use third-party advertisers to provide advertisements on our Service. This includes, but may not be limited to, the use of Google AdSense.

> • Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.  
>  • Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
>  • Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads Settings: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads>

## Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service. These Service Providers include, but may not be limited to: Google Analytics, Google Webmaster Tools, and Bing Webmaster Tools. These Service Providers allow Total Gaming Network to better respond to changes in traffic and website errors that include, but may not be limited to: Broken pages, server outages, or slow page loading. Both Google and Bing anonymize the data according to their own policies.

### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

### Bing Webmaster Tools

For more information on the privacy practices of (Bing) Microsoft, please visit the Microsoft Privacy Statement web page: <https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-US/privacystatement>

## Third-Party Registration

Total Gaming Network gives users the option to register to the Service using third-party authentication methods. These include Twitter, Google, and/or Facebook. Use of these third-party Services are optional. Use of these third-party Services is made voluntarily during registration. Use of these third-party Services facilitate registration at Total Gaming Network. Total Gaming Network does not require nor have access to any data that is outside of the scope of a normal user registration. Total Gaming Network does not request nor have access to any "write" capabilities on any of the aforementioned third-party Services.

### Twitter

Users may register at Total Gaming Network using their Twitter account via the Twitter API. We request only the most basic of permissions. We utilize only the most basic of information from Twitter to facilitate registration. This typically includes, but may not be limited to, information such as a user's email and age, which are required for all new user registrations. We do not require any additional permissions, nor do we need to "write" any data to a user's Twitter account in any capacity. While the authorization page for the Twitter API says that we will be able to "read Tweets from your timeline" and "see who you follow" we do not have any interest in doing either of those things.

For more information on the privacy practices of Twitter, please visit the Twitter Privacy Policy web page: <https://twitter.com/en/privacy>

### Facebook

Users may register at Total Gaming Network using their Facebook account via the Facebook API. We request only the most basic of permissions. We utilize only the most basic of information from Facebook to facilitate registration. This typically includes, but may not be limited to, information such as a user's email and age, which are required for all new user registrations. We do not require any additional permissions, nor do we need to "write" any data to a user's Facebook account in any capacity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit the Facebook Privacy Policy web page: <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

### Google

Users may register at Total Gaming Network using their Google account via OAuth and the Google API. We request only the most basic of permissions. We utilize only the most basic of information from Google to facilitate registration. This typically includes, but may not be limited to, information such as a user's email ange age, which are required for all new user registrations. Use of the Google OAuth may also pull your name and profile picture. We do not require any additional permissions, nor do we need to "write" any data to a user's Google account in any capacity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Twitter Privacy Policy web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

Users that are already registered at Total Gaming Network can connect to any of the above third-party Services at any time by visiting their User Settings when logged in: <https://totalgamingnetwork.com/settings/account>

Connecting to these third-party Services is completely optional and done so voluntarily. Users wishing to disconnect from any of the above third-party Services can do so by visiting their User Settings page when logged in: <https://totalgamingnetwork.com/settings/account>

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

We strive to protect your personal data at all costs. However, remember that no means of transmitting data over the internet, or any form of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable. As such, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by visiting this page on our website: <https://totalgamingnetwork.com/contact-us>
